Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Okay. lady. Two slices for you.
Come on.
Keno!
Yo. Keno!
Come on now. saddle up.
We got another order
for that O'Neil woman.
Are you kidding me?
Again?
She should be
buying it wholesale.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Keno. be careful.
Hey. ladies.
Which one of you lucky girls
gets a ride with me tonight?
Dream on. dweeb.
Yeah. okay.
But when i do. i'll dream
of something a little thinner.
April O'Neil.
That's nice.
- Stack it over here.
- Six boxes.
Hold it!
You guys are under arrest.
- What are you. night security?
- Well. no. Actually. i'm...
pizza delivery.
Cut me a break.
Down we go!
Stay down!
Did i mention
i study martial arts?
- Okay. let's move it.
- Hey. who's this guy?
- Let's get him.
- Help.
You're gonna need it. kid.
Come on.
- Let's get out of here!
- Let's go! Move it out! Move it!
Awesome!
Wicked!
Eclectic!
Eclectic? Geez!
Hey. look out!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
Sorry. kid.
it's for your own good.
Let me out of here!
Yeah!
Get along there. little doggie!
Rawhide! Robocop!
Come on!
Ninja cowboy!
Oh. you dudes
want to play too?
Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait!
Check this!
"Walk the Dog."
That's pretty good. huh?
And then.
"Around the World!"
Hey. hey. now you see 'em.
now you don't!
Missed!
Yeah. Yeah. yeah.
Yeah!
Missed me!
The missing link!
You want a pickle?
i'll give you a pickle!
Combat cold cuts!
Let's get out of here!
And next time
i'll use mustard!
Hey. Hey. dude.
Give me your hand.
Come on.
Who. what. where. huh?
Well. that leaves out
"why" and "when." doesn't it?
Yeah! It's a good thing we saw you
coming in here from the roof...
- Hey. Mikey!
- I mean from across the...
Look. kid. you can find a phone
and call the police. Are you okay?
- We'll start tying them up.
- Yeah. but...
Yeah. yeah. but good. Go!
- Kids.
Come on.
Okay. just hurry up.
There's a ton of these guys.
Okay. bye.
- Well. i hope we can find a cab.
- There are lots of cabs.
- Not at this time of night.
- Hey!
i know you. You're. uh...
- April O'Neil.
- April O'Neil. yeah.
The news lady.
So. how are things in
the action-news biz?
Pretty tiring. mostly.
Well. honey. if you cut back
on the heavy aerobics...
- And all that jumping and yelling...
- It's all right. Muriel.
- I find it disturbing.
- Let me get that for you.
Oh. right!
My... My aerobics.
- I'll do that. Bye.
- Good night. April.
- Was that necessary?
- I saw her on TV.
- A skirt walks by and...
- Will you stop it already?
Michaelangelo.
Leonardo.
Donatello...
and Raphael.
The rat is the cleanest one.
Oh. yeah!
Primo workout. dudes!
- Yeah!
- We showed those guys. huh?
- Muy primo. bros.
- Turtle-riffic!
Max-amundo.
A cappella!
Perestroika?
Okay. i got it. "Frerejacques."
FrereJacques
- FrereJacques
- Donny. give it up.
- Hi. guys.
- Yo. April!
What it is? Yeah!
- We brought-a dinner.
- Let's eat over here.
- Pizza. Again.
- Yup. Pepperoni.
Please. please.
A moment to reflect.
Here comes the slice.
- Enjoy.
- Ninja pizza!
Ninja pizza?
Pizza that vanish
quickly without trace.
- Here you go.
- Yo. Mikey. toss me a ninja slice!
Donny. Statue of Liberty!
- Come on. throw it! Over here!
- Mike. no!
i'm right here! He's at the forty!
He's at the twenty!
He looks. He rolls back.
He goes deep.
- Yeah!
- Donatello. stop!
Touchdown!
Yeah!
- Yeah!
So. any luck finding
a new place to live yet?
Well. you know. in this market
it's actually very difficult...
to find good
subterranean housing.
Hey. we could always go back
to the old sewer den.
- Well...
- Right. Raph. It's a little tough...
when about 500 members
of the Foot Clan...
- Know where you live.
- He's right.
We kicked their butts.
They're all in jail.
'Sides. we took out
the Shredder...
so what's everybody
so worried about?
He's right.
No. Splinter took out
the Shredder.
- They're both right.
- Yeah. yeah.
i was there. Leo.
Remember?
Old Shred did a swan dive
with a half gainer...
right into the back
of a garbage truck!
Come away from there!
Geez. i was just...
Never forget
who you are.
You are ninja. You must always
practice the art of invisibility.
- All of you.
- Well. i don't get it.
i mean. why? We saved the city.
Why can't we just go out and...
Stand before me. my sons.
For 15 years.
you have been confined below.
Now the outside world
beckons your teenage minds...
but they could
never understand.
Their world
can never be ours.
Not even pizza?
Pizza's okay.
Man. you give a guy
a heart attack.
Here. let me get
you guys some napkins.
- What for?
Take heart. child.
We will not be here much longer.
Oh. no. no. You guys can
stay here as long as you want.
- Oh. gee. Thanks a lot.
- No!
- We do not belong here above.
- Oh. man!
Yes. Master Splinter.
Hey! Ten flips now!
Go!
Kids.
- One.
Such energy is wasted.
- Two.
- Remember...
the true ninja is
a master of all things...
a master of his environment...
a master of himself.
Focus your thoughts
on where we must go...
and leave the Shredder buried.
Let's go!
Come on.
is this it?
Everyone else must've
been picked up.
Well. maybe they
didn't find us.
Hey. we all knew the junkyard
was our fallback spot.
Our father gone!
They will pay!
i. Tatsu. now lead.
Let any who challenge
step forward.
i challenge.
His face!
Master Shredder!
Choose the best man
from those that remain...
to follow the reporter.
She is the key to finding
the creatures that did this to me.
Yes. Master.
Next. Master.
we rebuild the Foot?
There is only
one thing next.
Revenge.
And in this day and age
of ecological abuse...
it's nice to find a company
that's doing something to help.
joining me on the final day
of their cleanup efforts...
is Techno Global Research
industries spokesman...
Professorjordan Perry.
Excuse me. Professor?
- Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon. Miss O'Neil.
Professor.
perhaps you can tell us...
why TGRi has finally decided
to clean up the waste...
that's been burying here for years.
Would you like me
to keep my answer succinct...
or will you be able to edit later on
in case i start to ramble...
- Which i'm in the habit of doing.
- Professor. we're live.
Oh. right. well. yes.
Our organization has always
been very concerned...
with the welfare
of the community we serve.
- Indeed. TGRI is...
- Man. who is this spasmatic?
Would you give the guy a break?
He's a scientist.
Yeah. fascinating.
Hey. isn't Oprah on?
Raph. just leave it.
We're watching April.
And dispose of them
in an ecologically more suitable way.
Hey. Mikey. do you think
you can crunch any louder?
i can still hear
out of this one.
Come on.
let's change this.
Hey. maybe somebody's got something
on our fight last night.
Do not change channel.
Reporting live from
Bayonne. NewJersey...
this is April O'Neil.
Channel Three News.
- Back to you.
- And that's it. We're off.
Great.
Thank you.
Professor. would you mind if i asked you
a few follow-up questions?
Not at all. Oh. drat!
You know. we're gonna
have to do it another time.
it's been a great pleasure
meeting you. Miss O'Neil.
All press members
must now clear the area.
Okay. great.
Report back at 3:00. okay?
- Enjoying your first day. Freddy?
- Yeah.
Hey. what were you
going to ask him?
Well. i don't know.
Don't worry about it.
i'm paid to be suspicious.
- Come on. come on.
- Oh. yeah. Sorry.
All non-TGRI employees
must now vacate the area.
Right here.
How could you
have missed this?
i don't know.
Grab some men.
i'll go find the professor.
We've got to
take care of this now.
- Go.
- Right.
All members of the press must
return their visitor badges...
at the main gate.
Dandelions?
Now. if the soil is
contaminated so far away...
there must be more leaky
canisters than we thought.
But how could that be?
They were only buried 15 years ago.
Fifteen. fifty. Just make sure
the rest are found and removed.
Maybe it wasn't such a good idea
to invite the press.
Sometimes the best way to hide
is right out in public.
if any of it fell
into the wrong hands...
i'm well aware of the risks.
Containment team. sector three.
This is not the reason
i sent you to follow her.
- No. Master. but i thought...
- Silence!
This may be even better.
Whatever caused this mutation
may be useful against my enemies.
Tatsu. gather your best men.
You have a mission tonight.
Hey. guys!
Check this!
Wax on. Wax off.
- Wax on...
- Mouth off!
- Hey. everyone's a critic.
- Hello?
Oh. man!
- April. you spoiled our surprise.
- We were gonna clean everything up.
Thanks. guys.
Where's Splinter?
He's been up on the roof
ever since he saw your report.
Really? Doing what?
Coming to a decision.
You've been meditating many hours.
Master Splinter.
Yes. and it is time.
join me above.
Maybe you better hear
what he has to say.
These last hours
have been spent...
pondering many questions.
Some are the very questions
of our origin.
The sewer.
Our transformation.
But the answers have
always remained...
hidden in the past...
veiled by a shadow
too deep to penetrate...
until now.
A light from the present...
reaches back
to illuminate that shadow.
You have never seen this.
but know what it is.
- That's the canister that had the ooze!
- That transformed us all.
i have kept it these 15 years.
But why do you only show us
now. Master Splinter?
TGRi!
The interview today.
i knew it!
i knew that there was something else
going on with those guys.
Yes. and we must know what...
for if the contents of this
canister were not unique...
the city may now face
grave danger.
After all these years.
After all this time
wondering who we are.
The past returns. my son.
it is time to seek our answers.
Disposed.
Well. you're the last one.
aren't you?
- Come on guys.
- I love this spy stuff.
Yeah.
Not much to this place.
it doesn't look like
there's any night security...
but we better
move in quiet.
- Yeah.
- Come on. Leo.
What do you say?
Let's do it. eh?
- Let's do it!
- Times Square city!
- I don't believe it!
- Like video games in 3-D!
- Totally massive!
Would you get a load
of this crazy joint!
The past returns. I knew
we'd find something special.
i'll say special.
Look at this.
- Hey. where do you put the quarter?
- Will you stop messing around?
Hey. guys. over there!
- What do you make of it. Donny?
- Well. i'm not sure.
Looks like just a bunch
of serial numbers.
Let's see. uh...
Disposed.
- Disposed.
- Hey. dudes. we're too late.
Like. uh. no deposit.
no return.
Well. except maybe this one.
What do you mean?
Look!
"Active."
- Yeah.
- Can you bring up the file?
Well. i could try.
But if the database is coded.
the whole system might go down.
- Do it!
- Yeah. yeah!
- Drag.
- Drat.
No. no. no! So close!
- What?
- The Foot!
He's got the canister!
- Get it!
- I got him!
Go. go. go. go!
- Throw it over here.
- Go long! Go long!
Down field!
Turtle in the open!
Ah. one. two. three. punt!
Hey. guys. huddle.
Come here. Come on.
Mikey. you go up the middle.
You guys take the sides.
- Got it.
- I don't get it.
Ready. break!
Hey. Mikey. surf's up. dude!
Wipe out!
Ninja vanish!
Oh. great!
Terrific!
Wonderful!
Bummer!
And this was the only one?
Then it's time to
find out exactly...
what this ooze can do.
isn't it. Professor?
We'll find a home soon. Paulina.
and then it'll be just you and me.
Now. look. we've all talked about it.
We've decided to do it...
- And that's all there is to it.
- But i don't understand.
You guys haven't even found
a new place to live yet.
it's too dangerous to stay here with you
when the Foot are out there. They might be
looking for us.
We could go looking for them
for a change.
i mean. they've got the ooze.
- First we move. then we look.
- I don't know about you guys...
- But i could really go for a slice of...
- Pizza!
Whoa! Spookular!
Miss O'Neil?
Wait! I'll be right there.
- What?
- I didn't order any pizza.
Oh. i know.
But the guy in 313 did...
and now he doesn't
seem to be there.
i figured since you
order so much anyway...
that. you know. maybe you...
- Where'd these come from?
- Those...
are mine!
Yeah. I...
i like to do a little chucking
every now and then.
Yeah.
i'd keep practicing.
On second thought.
why don't i take this pizza anyway?
i can always use more.
Let me get my wallet.
No. that's okay.
- Yes. please.
- Don't worry about it.
One last thing. though.
You might want to know about this!
- You guys!
- What's the big idea?
Can i hurt him? Please!
Tell me i can hurt him!
- Please. please!
- Take it easy.
i think you'd better sit down.
And with an old
Renaissance art book...
i found in a storm drain...
i gave them all names.
Yeah.
i'm Leonardo.
i'm Michaelangelo.
Donatello.
i'm Rafael.
Yeah. all the good ones
end in "O."
- Michaelangelo!
- Yeah?
- Go!
- All right.
i can't believe
every time i...
One.
- Two.
- Basically. what you're telling me...
is you guys were all slimed!
it wasn't slime. It was ooze.
And there's more of it out there.
- Where?
- We're not sure.
See. there's this sort of
clan of ninja thieves.
- A secret group. They call themselves...
- The Foot?
- You've heard of'em?
- The word is out...
that these guys are looking
for anybody they can find...
with martial arts talent.
especially teenagers.
Hey. and if i let myself get recruited.
guess what that might lead us to?
No way. Keno.
Forget about it.
Believe me. i really hate to say this.
but the kid's got a...
- No!
- Why not?
Too dangerous.
But i thought we...
Oh. man.
Twenty.
Twenty-one.
Twenty...
One? Yeah.
And these are the two most vicious
animals you could find?
Good.
- Professor?
- Preparations are complete. however...
- Begin!
- I must re-register my protest...
and remind you
of the immense danger if...
That's enough talk from me.
We'll begin.
Yes.
- Clear.
- Go. go. Move.
- See ya. April.
- Bye.
Wish us luck.
We'll be back for Splinter.
The lives of two people don't amount
to a hill of beans in this crazy world.
That's why you're
gettin' on that plane.
- Maybe not today. maybe not to...
- Would you stop!
See ya.
All right. hold it.
This is stupid.
We got the Foot up there
with the ooze...
and we're down here
playing "Century 21."
- Raph!
- Come on. Leo.
Even you could think of something
better to do than this.
i already have.
Now. let's get going!
That's it.
i'm goin' up.
- No. you're not!
- Let go of my arm. Leo.
Guys. guys. guys!
i just got an idea.
Two words that could solve
all our housing problems.
Time share!
- Not quite ripe yet.
- I'm outta here.
But... Oh. man!
Oh. boy.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
- Finding a home should be easy.
- But no!
You'd think even an idiot
could find a place down here.
But no...
Oh. no!
Mikey. buddy!
- Mikey. are you okay?
- Mikey!
Check it out!
Yeah!
- Whoa!
- Okay. bro? Come on. Leo!
- You all right?
- No prob.
Power! Yeah.
Oh. yeah!
Look. I don't believe this.
- Yes!
- Yes. yes!
it's like spider city!
Great!
Rock-a-bye-baby.
it's roomy!
And it's well hidden. huh?
So what do ya think?
You know. i hear the sewers
in Connecticut are really nice.
- Yeah. Come on.
- This is great!
- How much longer?
- Look. i told you. i don't know.
it takes time. Days!
i want them
as soon as possible.
- I told...
- Sit down!
Aren't these enough
for your vengeance?
The Foot have already
failed against them.
i have failed.
But the next time
will be different.
The next fight will be
freak against freak!
April. will you listen
just for a minute?
it's a ratings week!
Phil. i told you.
i am following up on TGRi.
There's more going on there
than we know.
Look. that story is over.
We need something solid.
Something fresh.
i mean. like... like this.
- She's busy right now.
- "Looking ahead.
- Swimsuits in the '90s"?
- My interest is peaked.
Phil. i gotta get going.
You are always so busy.
i'm the news manager here. April!
April. there's a call for you.
Tell them i'll call them back.
He sounds pretty insistent.
Says his name's Donny.
Listen. tell Donny that she's busy
with her news manager right now...
and that she can't...
Where are you guys?
Did you find a place to live yet?
Oh. yeah. but i...
it's not much right now.
but we'll bring you down.
We've only really
had time to get Splinter...
- And pick up a few essentials.
- Yeah!
The bare essentials!
Look. the reason why
we're calling is...
have you seen Raphael
by any chance?
Yeah. Has he stopped by
or anything?
No. Why? Is he missing?
You know. there's still more stuff
to help with. Michaelangelo!
Hey. i'm helping Donny!
Give me the phone.
Hey. give me that...
- So you haven't seen him at all?
- No. I haven't.
if she does. tell him thanks
for wasting our time!
'Cause instead of looking
for the Foot and the ooze...
like we should...
we gotta go out and look
for him instead.
- What was that?
- Leo says hi.
- Donny. give me the phone.
- If you do hear something...
- Let us know.
- I wanna talk to April! It's important!
- Gimme. gimme. gimme!
- All right. here.
April. it's Mikey.
i'd just like to say...
- Hello.
- Would you give me that!
The cells will
no longer hold them.
Remove the bar.
it's time they learn
who their master is.
Remove the bar
and leave us.
Come forth!
Wolf. Snapping turtle.
incredible!
Yes. Come forward.
Attack me. if you will.
When it is over.
you will call me "Master"!
- Mama? Oh. Mama!
- Oh. Mama!
- Mama.
Get off me!
Babies!
They are babies!
What did you expect?
They'd come out quoting Macbeth?
- They are stupid!
- They're not stupid. They're infants.
Okay. they're stupid infants.
Put that down!
Fortunately. they seem to have
imprinted you as their surrogate mother.
- Mama.
- They are of no use to me against a...
See that these two things...
are properly disposed of.
No. You can't do that.
They're living creatures.
Not for long.
Hey. no. no.
Wait. look.
They may be
intellectually inferior. but...
As you can see. they do have
other attributes.
Maybe i'll keep them
around after all.
- Hey. man. how's it going?
- Pretty good.
- Good to see you. man.
- What's up?
Did you just get here?
Okay. guys.
Listen up.
i'm only going
to tell youse once.
All of youse guys is gonna
have to take a little test.
Then. if you're good enough...
we let you into
the organization.
Any questions?
Okay. follow me.
- Let's go.
- Lead the way. man.
i knew this would work.
just remember. we get you in.
we find the Foot headquarters...
we get you out to tell
the others. right?
Gee. maybe i should
write this down.
What?
i'm being punished. aren't i?
- Keno. wasn't it?
- Yeah.
You seem to be the only one
worthy of a final test.
You'll have 15 seconds to remove
as many of the bells as you can.
One sound and you fail.
And another thing.
we work in concealment.
Fifteen seconds.
Go!
is this enough?
Yeah!
Welcome to our headquarters.
Get yourself a training dogi
and meet me back in the yard.
Yeah. right.
Keno. come on.
Okay. Looks like
this is the place.
Yeah. looks like it.
First chance we get.
we're out of here.
What? What is it?
i thought i just saw a ghost.
Come on.
- What are we looking for anyway?
- Quiet. You want to get us...
caught?
Yeah. well...
Hi. We were lookin' for
a muffler for a '77 Chevy.
Whatever happened
to service with a smile?
Yeah!
Get out of here kid.
Go tell the others. Go now!
Hey. nice shot.
You're good.
Come on.
- I'm not gonna just...
- Run. or i'll kick your butt.
Move!
Come on. you guys!
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Come on.
Missed.
i'm curious.
Any of you guys ever heard
the expression "fair fight"?
You know. pal.
if i had a face like yours...
i'd try to make up for it
with some sort of a personality.
Come on.
Come on. April. Leo!
if you're there.
it's me. Keno.
Darn. Come on.
Raph's in trouble.
April. where are they?
- It's Raph.
- Wait. calm down. What happened?
i've gotta tell the guys.
They got him!
Who has got him?
Come on.
- Just like Keno said.
- Yeah.
- The perimeter's quiet.
A little too quiet.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Knock. knock.
- Well. that was easy.
- Yeah. a little too easy.
Look. it's Raph!
Yeah. a little too Raph.
You guys. knock it off.
Keep your eyes peeled.
i don't like this.
- Let's go.
- Right.
You know. given the layout
of this junkyard...
and the proximity
of certain structures...
if they were gonna
spring a trap...
they'd probably do it
right about...
Let us out of here!
What the...
The Shred dude!
it's him!
i've been waiting for you.
i have a little surprise.
- Oh. no.
- I don't like this.
i wonder what those are for.
Does the word "turtle-kabob"
mean anything to you?
Yeah. right!
Get your arm out of my face.
Patience.
First them...
then you.
You know. these nets
are remarkably effective.
Very well constructed.
Remind me to drop a line
to Ralph Nader!
Wait for my signal
to drop them.
i never got to see Paris.
A little closer.
A little closer!
Oh. we're almost there!
Get ready!
Cowabunga!
That's right. Shredder.
You forgot.
- We carry insurance.
- Mutual of Splinter. dude.
Get them!
Why don't you just
rip my lips off?
- You'd think...
- Enough.
Here. let me get this first.
Can we talk?
Guess not!
Pitiful.
You win.
- Looks like we're on our own.
- All right!
Tokka!
Rahzar!
Didn't we see these guys
on Wrestlemania?
Prove yourselves to me!
Attack!
Well. you know
what they say.
The bigger they are...
The more bones
they break.
- These guys are mine.
- Go get 'em. Donny.
All right. you overgrown.
ugly excuse for a turtle!
You know. maybe that "ugly" crack
was a little bit out of line.
Oh. that hurt!
Hey. you're that TGRi guy.
Hang on.
- I've got to get the hang of that.
- It's okay.
i'm gonna get you
out of here.
What?
Oh. am i glad to see you!
- Hey. guys. over here!
- Yeah! We're on our way.
Come on. Professor.
We don't have a lot of time.
- Hey. Mikey. we got the TGRi guy.
- Come on. come on.
- Well. actually. i'd rather not.
- Come on!
Step up to the bar. boys!
This way. Leo.
Come on.
You all right. Doc?
- Way to go. Mikey!
- Come on. You go next.
Come here.
- Come on. Raph.
- Yeah. yeah.
Stop them!
- Drop right in. Leo.
- All right!
Hey. look at this!
Stupid!
Come on. We gotta
meet back up with Splinter.
Yeah.
Four walking. talking turtles!
Yeah. the guy's Ph.D. material.
all right.
You're so intelligent.
it's incredible.
Don't freak. dude.
We can explain. You see...
Fifteen years ago.
you came into contact...
with a green colloidal gel
down in a sewer...
which transformed you
into your present state.
Fantastic!
There you go.
Come on. Yeah.
Amazing. guys.
i thought all the really
good dungeons were in Europe.
There you go. dude.
- This is wonderful!
- Yeah. okay.
We'll give you the tour later.
Right now we've got a few questions.
- A few inquiries.
- Yeah. a few...
- We'll give you a tour later.
- Give him room to speak.
The professor has much
to tell us.
Of course. laboratories
were crude back then...
and an accident was
just waiting to happen.
Wait a minute.
You mean to tell us...
that the formation of the ooze
was all just a big mistake?
Let me see.
Donatello. isn't it?
An unknown mixture
of discarded chemicals...
was accidentally exposed
to a series of radiated waves...
and the resulting ooze
was found to have remarkable...
but dangerous
mutanagenic properties.
Big mistake.
- Please continue. Professor.
- Yeah.
Well. on our way to bury them.
a near collision caused us...
to lose one of the canisters
down a sewer 15 years ago.
Professor Perry.
what's happening at TGRi now?
i imagine they're trying
to remove any evidence...
of the disposal process
and evacuate the premises...
which is standard procedure
when a mishap occurs.
And as we know. one or two
rather big mishaps have occurred.
Yeah.
Tokka. Rahzar and the Shredder.
And he's obsessed
with destroying you all.
Yeah. we got that impression.
all right.
- Michaelangelo.
- Yeah?
- Show the professor where he may rest.
- Righty-o!
This way. dude.
it ain't the Hilton. Let's face it. You'd
be better off staying at the Hilton.
What troubles you. my son?
i don't know. I just always thought
there'd be more to it...
to the ooze...
to. you know. us!
i know.
i always thought
there'd be something. i thought we'd
find out we were special.
Do not confuse the specter
of your origin...
with your present worth.
my sons.
i don't believe him!
There's just got to be more to it!
Perhaps the search
for a beginning...
rarely has so easy an end.
But our search
will have to wait.
Tonight's encounter
has left us with...
larger problems.
i got 'em.
Go. Play. Have fun.
Fun!
Tonight we leave a calling card
for the turtles.
Tomorrow we force
a final confrontation.
- Master say have fun!
- Fun!
Look. Sophie.
Some animals are knocking down
the telephone poles.
What do we do
if they come over here?
Let them get
their own cab.
Damage is minimal.
And as always. our official report
will be released...
after a thorough investigation.
Thank you. Miss O'Neil.
i have no further comments
at this time.
We will be in touch.
More as it develops.
Here you go.
Chief Sterns. i wonder
if i might ask you...
a few more questions
off-the-record.
Miss O'Neil. my record.
on-the-record...
clearly shows that i have
no off-the-record record.
- Make a record of that.
- Wait.
Were there any large tooth
or claw marks found here today?
How did you know...
that i don't know
what you're talking about?
i have reason to believe
this damage was caused by two... two...
really big animals.
And what type of animals
might these be. Miss O'Neil?
- Well. i can't say exactly.
- I see.
Then what leads you
to believe they did this?
i can't say that either. but...
Anything else you'd
like not to tell me?
Sterns. there are two very
dangerous things out there!
And just what exactly
would you like me to do about it?
i don't know.
i guess you're not the ones...
that are gonna have
to handle this.
That's what we do best.
Miss O'Neil.
Have a nice day.
Get sanitation
down here.
Get this place
cleaned up.
- Where's Freddy?
- He took off. Said he was sick.
- What do you need?
- Nothing. I can get it.
Hello. April.
Freddy?
Our master has a message
for your friends.
- Are you sure you weren't...
- They're not following me.
They don't need to.
They said
if you don't meet them...
at the construction
site tonight...
What?
he'd send Tokka
and Rahzar out again.
This time
into Central Park.
Oh. man! Central Park?
How are they going
to avoid all those people?
Then there is no choice...
but to meet as
the Shredder wishes.
He's just trying
to force you guys...
- Into fighting Tokka and Rahzar again.
- We know.
- You can't!
- April. there's no other way.
- You guys don't stand a chance.
- Wait!
Wait just a minute.
There might be a way.
- Temperature?
- 338 Kelvin.
Michaelangelo. pass me
the dimethyl chlorinide.
That.
You know. not to criticize
science or anything...
but wouldn't it be easier
to call it "the pink one"?
Donatello.
continue aeration.
Continuing aeration.
Man!
This stuff is rank.
Yeah. try carrying it
on the subway sometime.
i never got a seat
so fast in my life.
- Thanks for doing the shopping for us.
- No problem.
i hope you didn't mind me
picking up a few pies.
You're forgiven.
Are you sure
this stuff will work?
When i contaminated the ooze
used to transform Tokka and Rahzar...
making them intellectually inferior
and less dangerous...
i had no idea...
i'd be trying to create an anti-mutagen
based on that contamination.
Oh. anti-mutagen.
- What?
- He's not sure.
Pepperoni heaven!
Gentlemen. may i have
your attention?
- Leonardo. hand me a glass. please?
- Oh. yeah. Sure.
i got it.
Are you sure this stuff
will do the trick?
We won't know until
we spray those guys.
- Well. actually...
- "Actually" what?
Actually...
ingestion is
the only course.
- What?
- You mean. they have to eat it?
Affirmative.
Yes. Right on. my man.
Great!
That should be easy.
Any ideas?
We could solidify it
in ice-cube trays.
Well. i've got an idea.
Hey. is this gonna work?
is. like. Schwarzenegger
hard to spell?
Yeah.
- Pretty quiet.
- Yeah.
Shredder!
Thanks. Raph. I may never
have the hiccups again.
Welcome.
All we need now is...
- Wide World of Sports and a blimp.
- How ironic.
The very thing
that was your making...
will now be your undoing.
Tokka! Rahzar!
Let the games begin!
Watch out.
What? Leo. come here!
Come on! Go get 'em!
Wait!
First we should observe
the ancient ritual of the...
- Traditional pre-fight doughnut.
- Yeah.
Pre-fight doughnut?
- Why did i let you talk me into this?
- Give it a chance.
Hi. guys.
- It's not gonna work.
- Yes. it is. They'll eat anything.
Oh. yes!
Nummers. Yeah.
Good boy.
A little drooly.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
- Yeah! Good boy.
- Yeah. right.
- Go on.
Here you go. Yeah.
in your mouth.
Wolf it down! Scarf it!
- Have another.
- Eat it. Yeah. It'll be great!
- They found the cubes.
- I told you it wasn't gonna work.
Get them!
i never touched it!
Can't we talk this out?
No. wait! Wait!
Major spin cycle!
Hey. Leo!
Mikey?
Maybe i should've
brought bagels!
Now i know what a postal
package feels like.
Hey. Mikey. you okay?
- You take the ugly one.
- No. you take the ugly one.
- I'll take the ugly one!
- Which one's the ugly one?
Get back! Go on! Go on!
Hey. come here.
You want some more?
Come on.
Look at those costumes!
i love this place!
Hey. you!
Table for one!
Man. could this
get any worse?
Oh. foul!
Nasty!
Hey. nice tie. bro.
Do you mind? Come on!
Big brown ugly dude.
i'm over here.
Try to get me.
Yo. it's
the green machine
Gonna rock the town
without bein'seen
Have you ever seen
a turtle get down
Slammin'and jammin'to the new
swing sound. yeah. everybody
Let's move. Vanilla is here
with the NewJack groove
Gonna rock and roll the place
with the power of the ninja turtle bass
Iceman. you know
I'm not playin'
Devastate the show...
- Professor!
- It would appear the anti-mutagen...
- Has been somewhat ineffective.
- No kidding.
We've gotta do something.
Come on.
Go. ninja
Go. ninja. go
What is this?
i didn't order any extras.
- Did you order any extras?
- Well...
Where did these
extras come from?
Get me a phone.
i want the police. Now.
Phone. Police.
Go! Hurry up!
Nice swing!
This is bad.
Carbon dioxide...
is essential to
the anti-mutanagenic process.
Their burping is probably
retarding the reaction.
isn't there any way
to speed it back up?
The reintroduction of CO2
could act as a catalyst.
- The problem is finding a ready supply.
- Yeah.
Genius. Pure genius.
i can't take this anymore!
We should be out there
with the guys!
No. You have youth.
i have experience.
But only those
who now fight have both.
- But i can fight.
- They fight because they must...
but it is the last choice
for the true ninja.
Used unwisely. it becomes
a double-edged sword.
Look. i know you're trying to help me.
but you can't keep me here.
i cannot.
You sure about this.
Donny?
- Don't worry. Just do it.
- Right.
Come on. guys. Come on.
Come on. come on.
Over here. big guy.
- Okay. Mikey?
- Yeah!
Raph. now!
Rock and roll!
- Do it. Donny.
- Open wide!
- Say "ahh."
- Go. ninja. go. ninja. go
Go. ninja
Go. ninja. go
i think it's working!
These dudes are copping
major Z's already.
- All right!
- Yeah!
What?
- It's the police.
- The police? What are you doing?
They like it.
They like it!
- Go. go. go. go. go!
- It's okay. They like it.
The Foot!
it's party time. boys!
i win. You lose.
It's the green machine gonna rock
the town without bein'seen
Have you ever seen
a turtle get down
Slammin'and jammin'
to the new swing sound
One kick. two kick.
three kick. four!
We're gonna
rock and roll the place
With the power of
the ninja turtle bass
Iceman. you know
I'm not playin'
Devastate the show
while the turtles are sayin'
Ninja. ninja rap
Wishbone crunch on two!
Hutt. hutt. wow!
Villains. you better
run and hide
Because one day
you might not slide
So choose your weapon
Don't slip
Ninja. ninja. rap
Go. go. go. go
Go. ninja
Go. ninja. go
Go. go. go. go
Ninja. ninja go
Sock it to me. baby!
Go. go. go. go
Ninja. ninja. rap
We're shakin'! Yeah!
You like what you saw?
Then give it up
for us turtles!
Go. ninja
Go. ninja. go
Yeah!
Ninja! Ninja!
We're not through yet!
just save yourself
the trouble. Shredder. It's all over.
The battle is yours.
but the war is far from over.
Not so long
as i possess this.
The green stuff.
- Hand it over. Shredder.
- Of course.
in small doses
through future mutants.
- You'll have to get through us first!
- Yeah!
A pleasure.
Guys. i'm here.
Get out of my way.
- Get out! Watch out!
- Let us handle it. Keno.
Let me go!
Keno. stay back.
- Raph. get on my back.
- Fool!
- Back!
- You're not going anywhere. Shredder!
On the contrary.
We're going somewhere.
- Donny. come on!
- If you try to stop us...
i'll cover her with this.
Let me go.
i can take him! Come on!
Full volume.
Keno. it's not your fight.
- Hit it. Mikey!
- Rock and roll!
is she all right?
- Keno. i told you...
- I know. This is not my fight.
- At last!
- Come on. Let's go.
- I'm coming.
- I learned that from a rat.
Later. Keno. dude!
Tokka and Rahzar.
How cute.
Hey. We could make
a fortune in the diet racket.
Oh. Mikey.
- Maybe he set a distance record.
- Doubtful.
Hey. where'd he go?
- Anything?
- Nothing.
Well. dudes. i'd say
that's pretty much a wrap.
Cowabunga?
- Cowabunga!
- Yeah!
Cowabunga!
- The last vial of ooze!
- He must have drank all of it.
it's a super Shredder.
Great! Now what
are we supposed to do?
This thing can't take much more of this.
not with all that stuff on top.
Shredder. you got
to listen to reason!
You're gonna
destroy us all!
Then so be it!
You okay?
it's all coming down!
Watch your head. guys!
We're pancakes!
A true ninja is a master
of himself and his environment.
So don't forget.
We're turtles!
i've said it before.
and i'll say it again.
"Man. i love
being a turtle!"
- Too bad the Shredder can't say that.
- Yeah.
- Look!
- Wha...
it can't be.
Nobody could
have survived that.
That's the end
of the Shredder.
- Yeah.
And in a bizarre
final note...
to the mysterious
disappearance of TGRI...
this message was delivered
to the station earlier today.
'"To Leonardo.
Michaelangelo. Raphael...
- And Donatello...
- Idiots.
thanks for
your help. dudes.
Signed.
ProfessorJordan Perry. "
Of course we can only
guess at its meaning.
And now this.
Bodacious!
- Ostentatious!
- Hey. hey. spacious!
Hey. dudes!
Cowabunga says it all!
Cowabunga!
Oh. yeah!
We're home.
Were you seen?
- Of course not. Master Splinter.
- We practice ninja.
The art of invisibility.
Practice harder.
Ten flips now!
And remember...
"Go. ninja
Go. ninja. go!"
i made another funny!
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-